[{"answer": "I don't know -- I don't think between want to kill each other, but I want to win.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "You want to kill each other in the final don't you?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "A failure, a total starving (ph) failure.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "What did you think you'd be when you were young?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "In a different life, different world, it would have worked out very well.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "Did you ever imagine being married to Mary Tyler Moore?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): It's extremely stressful.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "And, Marlee, it's so stressful, isn't it?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): And yet it's up to you whether you want to take it that way.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "They're trying to break down you defenses, they're trying to get you emotionally and physically shattered, aren't they?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): I raised $1,150,000.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "And what were the charities?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "I'm just under $800,000 for Saint Jude's Research Hospital, and then another $130,000 for other charities.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "John?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): Well, exactly, I mean for me, the whole point for me was to do it for charity because I mean, clearly, it is exposure, people want to see what you can do beyond what they expect, what you might do in your career.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "There are other reasons, it certainly makes you feel good when you can raise that kind of money, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): Perhaps because they see me signing and they know that's it's me talking.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Does it give you an advantage that the others heard you speaking in a male voice?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): Well, he loves it when he hears his own voice talking about him like that so --", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "And how embarrassed does he get when he has to talk about himself in the third person like this?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "I look at it as kind of like a privilege to experience being around such a relationship because how many people have ever even seen something like this in person.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "It's amazing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "It's bigger than big.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "There's a quarter of a million dollars that could go to your charity, it's a really big deal, isn't it?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "What I'm surprised is that -- and you would never think a reality TV show would give you a life lesson, but it truly has to me.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Putting the charity to one side, are you surprised how competitive you became in this competition, in the sense of wanting to win?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): I think -- well, coming into the show, I knew that I would be -- I mean, I would first try to raise as much money as I can for my charity, which again is The Starkey Hearing Foundation based in Minnesota.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Mostly incredibly hard work, mental challenges, competition with often erratic people what did you learn about yourselves and your character?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): You know, the financial crisis, it is what it is.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "You have these four children, and yet you've been hit while you've been doing this show by a big financial crisis in your life, haven't you?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "I mean yes, if you're Little John out there John Rich is my mate.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "What am I going to do?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not real impressed with that.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): I would hope that it would give me the recognition of showing who I am in real life.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Marlee, what do you hope this show will do for you?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I think there's a stereotype that comes with cowboy hats.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "John what do you think?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): I've had my husband for 18 years, I've had four kids with him, and I'm an extremely happily married woman --", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "And, Marlee, typical question for you, but I'm going to ask you anyway, if you could live without one of two men, your husband or Jack -- who would it be?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "You should just leave the set.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): You mean deal with what, my celebrity or my deafness, or me going away --", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "How do your children deal with it?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): They don't know any other way.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "How do you converse with them?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): They sign if they feel like it.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Can they all do the sign language?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": ", (through interpreter): No, listen, I can't -- that's actually a good point.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "If they don't want to listen to their mother, they don't bother, right?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "I would've like to have seen him in a debate.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "What do you think President Trump would've been like for this country?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "(through translator): You know, I'm stunned, but I'm more eager to roll up my sleeves and just jump in it and see what you got for us.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "What do you think Marlee?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): Yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "But let's just -- let's cut the crap shall we, you both want to kill each other in the final right?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "I don't about -- I don't think we want to kill each other, but I want to win.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "You want to kill each other in the final don't you?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "You are, because every Christmas in Britain, I sort of familiar regime.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I can do the bad one that I did.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Can you still do that God awful Cockney accent that you did?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Don't pretend to be me.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "I don't think I can -- what would be a line?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Have you been to the Cockney part of London?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Do they laugh at you or with you?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "What do you think your great talent is?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "A failure, a total starving failure.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What did you think you would be when you were younger?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Oh, 25 -- more than 25 years now.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "You have been clean for how long now?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Having a hangover so bad that I could hardly -- shaking, splitting headaches, and having to go to work.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "How bad was it at its worst for you?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "I probably -- that was -- eight, ten drinks.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "How much would you be drinking?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Were you?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Very uneasy, yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Did that make you feel slightly uneasy?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "AN DYKE: No.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "You never had a drink again?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Don't miss it all.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "Do you wish you could have a glass of wine over a meal or something?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "I had a doctor tell me I had an emphysema scar, a man I didn't even know, a little East Indian doctor.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Why did you give up cigarettes?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "Only your mother would think --", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "How about the baby?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "In my case, extremely important.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "How important -- obviously it's important, but how important is chemistry between a leading man and lady?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Mary Tyler Moore.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Mary Tyler Moore?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "In a different life, in a different world, it probably would have worked out very well, yeah.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Could you have ever imagined being married to Mary Tyler Moore?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "It's a surprise to me because I'm still -- I just did a show where I danced and sang.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "How can Dick Van Dyke be 85?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Obama.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Which of all of them impressed you the most?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "He was so cordial.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "ORGAN: Why?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "Oh yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "That's quite something, isn't it?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "Well, I've retired hundreds of times and it never worked out.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Why don't you say I'm going to go lie by the pool?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "Because I enjoy -- I enjoy it.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Are you proud of yourself?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "AN DYKE: You have to care about the welfare of the other person.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "What do you think the secret of true love is?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "Three.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "How many times have you had that feeling?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "Do you think you may ever get remarried?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "You're never going to give up, are you, Dick?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "Did you meet the president?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "Hi, I'm Barack.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 753, "question": "What did he say you?", "qSentId": 752}, {"answer": "He did.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "He didn't say that?", "qSentId": 754}, {"answer": "I had no idea at the time when I met him.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 765, "question": "When was the moment -- when Michelle was dating Barack, when was the moment that you realized this guy may be something special politically?", "qSentId": 764}, {"answer": "I don't know -- I don't think between want to kill each other, but I want to win.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "ORGAN: You want to kill each other in the final don't you?", "qSentId": 786}, {"answer": "A failure, a total starving (ph) failure.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 793, "question": "What did you think you'd be when you were young?", "qSentId": 792}, {"answer": "In a different life, different world, it would have worked out very well.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 798, "question": "Did you ever imagine being married to Mary Tyler Moore?", "qSentId": 797}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): It's extremely stressful.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "And, Marlee, it's so stressful, isn't it?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): And yet it's up to you whether you want to take it that way.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "They're trying to break down you defenses, they're trying to get you emotionally and physically shattered, aren't they?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): I raised $1,150,000.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 841, "question": "And what were the charities?", "qSentId": 840}, {"answer": "I'm just under $800,000 for Saint Jude's Research Hospital, and then another $130,000 for other charities.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "John?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): Well, exactly, I mean for me, the whole point for me was to do it for charity because I mean, clearly, it is exposure, people want to see what you can do beyond what they expect, what you might do in your career.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 851, "question": "There are other reasons, it certainly makes you feel good when you can raise that kind of money, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 850}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): Perhaps because they see me signing and they know that's it's me talking.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 891, "question": "Does it give you an advantage that the others heard you speaking in a male voice?", "qSentId": 890}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): Well, he loves it when he hears his own voice talking about him like that so --", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 908, "question": "And how embarrassed does he get when he has to talk about himself in the third person like this?", "qSentId": 907}, {"answer": "I look at it as kind of like a privilege to experience being around such a relationship because how many people have ever even seen something like this in person.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 919, "question": "It's amazing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 918}, {"answer": "It's bigger than big.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 947, "question": "There's a quarter of a million dollars that could go to your charity, it's a really big deal, isn't it?", "qSentId": 946}, {"answer": "What I'm surprised is that -- and you would never think a reality TV show would give you a life lesson, but it truly has to me.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 957, "question": "Putting the charity to one side, are you surprised how competitive you became in this competition, in the sense of wanting to win?", "qSentId": 956}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): I think -- well, coming into the show, I knew that I would be -- I mean, I would first try to raise as much money as I can for my charity, which again is The Starkey Hearing Foundation based in Minnesota.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 972, "question": "Mostly incredibly hard work, mental challenges, competition with often erratic people what did you learn about yourselves and your character?", "qSentId": 971}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): You know, the financial crisis, it is what it is.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1048, "question": "You have these four children, and yet you've been hit while you've been doing this show by a big financial crisis in your life, haven't you?", "qSentId": 1047}, {"answer": "I mean yes, if you're Little John out there John Rich is my mate.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1081, "question": "What am I going to do?", "qSentId": 1080}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not real impressed with that.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1107, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 1106}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): I would hope that it would give me the recognition of showing who I am in real life.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1113, "question": "Marlee, what do you hope this show will do for you?", "qSentId": 1112}, {"answer": "I think there's a stereotype that comes with cowboy hats.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1118, "question": "John what do you think?", "qSentId": 1117}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): I've had my husband for 18 years, I've had four kids with him, and I'm an extremely happily married woman --", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1126, "question": "And, Marlee, typical question for you, but I'm going to ask you anyway, if you could live without one of two men, your husband or Jack -- who would it be?", "qSentId": 1125}, {"answer": "You should just leave the set.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1136, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 1135}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): You mean deal with what, my celebrity or my deafness, or me going away --", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1152, "question": "How do your children deal with it?", "qSentId": 1151}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): They don't know any other way.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1155, "question": "How do you converse with them?", "qSentId": 1154}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): They sign if they feel like it.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1159, "question": "Can they all do the sign language?", "qSentId": 1158}, {"answer": ", (through interpreter): No, listen, I can't -- that's actually a good point.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1162, "question": "If they don't want to listen to their mother, they don't bother, right?", "qSentId": 1161}, {"answer": "I would've like to have seen him in a debate.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1175, "question": "What do you think President Trump would've been like for this country?", "qSentId": 1174}, {"answer": "(through translator): You know, I'm stunned, but I'm more eager to roll up my sleeves and just jump in it and see what you got for us.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1225, "question": "What do you think Marlee?", "qSentId": 1224}, {"answer": "(through interpreter): Yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1245, "question": "But let's just -- let's cut the crap shall we, you both want to kill each other in the final right?", "qSentId": 1244}, {"answer": "I don't about -- I don't think we want to kill each other, but I want to win.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1249, "question": "You want to kill each other in the final don't you?", "qSentId": 1248}, {"answer": "You are, because every Christmas in Britain, I sort of familiar regime.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1276, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 1275}, {"answer": "I can do the bad one that I did.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1282, "question": "Can you still do that God awful Cockney accent that you did?", "qSentId": 1281}, {"answer": "Don't pretend to be me.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1287, "question": "I don't think I can -- what would be a line?", "qSentId": 1286}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1297, "question": "Have you been to the Cockney part of London?", "qSentId": 1296}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1300, "question": "Do they laugh at you or with you?", "qSentId": 1299}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1307, "question": "What do you think your great talent is?", "qSentId": 1306}, {"answer": "A failure, a total starving failure.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1319, "question": "What did you think you would be when you were younger?", "qSentId": 1318}, {"answer": "Oh, 25 -- more than 25 years now.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1333, "question": "You have been clean for how long now?", "qSentId": 1332}, {"answer": "Having a hangover so bad that I could hardly -- shaking, splitting headaches, and having to go to work.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1355, "question": "How bad was it at its worst for you?", "qSentId": 1354}, {"answer": "I probably -- that was -- eight, ten drinks.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1357, "question": "How much would you be drinking?", "qSentId": 1356}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1365, "question": "Were you?", "qSentId": 1364}, {"answer": "Very uneasy, yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1369, "question": "Did that make you feel slightly uneasy?", "qSentId": 1368}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1372, "question": "You never had a drink again?", "qSentId": 1371}, {"answer": "Don't miss it all.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1380, "question": "Do you wish you could have a glass of wine over a meal or something?", "qSentId": 1379}, {"answer": "I had a doctor tell me I had an emphysema scar, a man I didn't even know, a little East Indian doctor.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1385, "question": "Why did you give up cigarettes?", "qSentId": 1384}, {"answer": "Only your mother would think --", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1407, "question": "How about the baby?", "qSentId": 1406}, {"answer": "In my case, extremely important.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1425, "question": "How important -- obviously it's important, but how important is chemistry between a leading man and lady?", "qSentId": 1424}, {"answer": "Mary Tyler Moore.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1435, "question": "Mary Tyler Moore?", "qSentId": 1434}, {"answer": "In a different life, in a different world, it probably would have worked out very well, yeah.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1442, "question": "Could you have ever imagined being married to Mary Tyler Moore?", "qSentId": 1441}, {"answer": "It's a surprise to me because I'm still -- I just did a show where I danced and sang.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1450, "question": "How can Dick Van Dyke be 85?", "qSentId": 1449}, {"answer": "Obama.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1457, "question": "Which of all of them impressed you the most?", "qSentId": 1456}, {"answer": "He was so cordial.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1460, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 1459}, {"answer": "Oh yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1472, "question": "That's quite something, isn't it?", "qSentId": 1471}, {"answer": "Well, I've retired hundreds of times and it never worked out.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1476, "question": "Why don't you say I'm going to go lie by the pool?", "qSentId": 1475}, {"answer": "Because I enjoy -- I enjoy it.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1478, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 1477}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1492, "question": "Are you proud of yourself?", "qSentId": 1491}, {"answer": "You have to care about the welfare of the other person.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1501, "question": "What do you think the secret of true love is?", "qSentId": 1500}, {"answer": "Three.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1503, "question": "How many times have you had that feeling?", "qSentId": 1502}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1510, "question": "Do you think you may ever get remarried?", "qSentId": 1509}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1515, "question": "You're never going to give up, are you, Dick?", "qSentId": 1514}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1527, "question": "Did you meet the president?", "qSentId": 1526}, {"answer": "Hi, I'm Barack.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1530, "question": "What did he say you?", "qSentId": 1529}, {"answer": "He did.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1532, "question": "He didn't say that?", "qSentId": 1531}, {"answer": "I had no idea at the time when I met him.", "docId": "110520pmt", "aSentId": 1542, "question": "When was the moment -- when Michelle was dating Barack, when was the moment that you realized this guy may be something special politically?", "qSentId": 1541}]